 const QuestionsList = [
    {
      question: "I am standing between #26 & #169, who am I?",
      answer:"Spider-Man",
      options: [
        { label: "Spider-Man", value: "Spider-Man" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "Josh likes my style & Pranksy gave birth to me, who am I?",
      answer:"BAYC #5883",
      options: [
        { label: "BAYC #5883", value: "BAYC #5883" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "On a certain elemental table, my home is 36. Who am I?",
      answer:"Superman Funko #7",
      options: [
        { label: "Superman Funko #7", value: "Superman Funko #7" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        "After 324 days, the end of 4he first hour will bring oblivion. Our utopia created pain5takingly by the Emperor will be gone forever. N0t even I, a bad as2 d3m0n can save it.",
      answer:"ON1 #4502",
      options: [
        { label: "ON1 #4502", value: "ON1 #4502" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        "I look like I come from somewhere in Asia, but I'm from somewhere else. To find me, burn some paper and check the temperature.",
      answer:"Wicked Cranium #451",
      options: [
        { label: "Wicked Cranium #451", value: "Wicked Cranium #451" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        "Before the change, TSFUF QPFHQT was a pretty good artist. Maybe he would have created a piece for us to collect.",
        answer:"Steve Rogers, Captain America (a simple alphabet shift, cipher)",
      options: [
        {
          label:
            "Steve Rogers, Captain America (a simple alphabet shift, cipher)",
          value:
            "Steve Rogers, Captain America (a simple alphabet shift, cipher)",
        },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "It’s all relative. The one stone. 3141879-4181955.",
      answer:"Albert Einstein (one stone- einstein & the numbers are his DOB and DoD)debating whether to remove the ‘one stone’ clue as I feel it makes it a bit too easy, what do you think",
      options: [
        {
          label:
            "Albert Einstein (one stone- einstein & the numbers are his DOB and DoD)debating whether to remove the ‘one stone’ clue as I feel it makes it a bit too easy, what do you think",
          value:
            "Albert Einstein (one stone- einstein & the numbers are his DOB and DoD)debating whether to remove the ‘one stone’ clue as I feel it makes it a bit too easy, what do you think",
        },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        "THey were my theRApist, UNtiL thEy QuIt cuZ they fElL for a MadmaN. I realLy miss them.",
        answer:"Harleen Quinzell aka Harley Quinn (find and unscramble the capitalized letters...a couple don't fit)",
      options: [
        {
          label:
            "Harleen Quinzell aka Harley Quinn (find and unscramble the capitalized letters...a couple don't fit)",
          value:
            "Harleen Quinzell aka Harley Quinn (find and unscramble the capitalized letters...a couple don't fit)",
        },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "Let's not forget the living? A boy, his dog and ___",
      answer:"The plant under the desk",
      options: [
        { label: "The plant under the desk", value: "The plant under the desk" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        " Let's go to Ithaca with Todd Phillips. Oh wait, this isn't that movie. This artwork was created by a guy with a vampire Disney Avatar for his Collection that reminds me of Lemmy Kilmister.",
      answer:"Road Trip- Brian Morris Motor Head Collection",
      options: [
        {
          label: "Road Trip- Brian Morris Motor Head Collection",
          value: "Road Trip- Brian Morris Motor Head Collection",
        },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "Touch me, and nothing can touch you... ",
      answer:"Starman from Mario",
      options: [
        { label: "Starman from Mario", value: "Starman from Mario" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: " The answer to clue is in this limerick",
      answer:"The Hunt is almost over If you can find the pretender This antihero Is no longer a zero But still wants to be an Avenger.Deadpool statue",
      options: [
        {
          label:"The Hunt is almost over If you can find the pretender This antihero Is no longer a zero But still wants to be an Avenger.Deadpool statue",
          value:"The Hunt is almost over If you can find the pretender This antihero Is no longer a zero But still wants to be an Avenger.Deadpool statue"
        },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question:
        "I share a name with the man who created many of the guys on the shelves above me. I'm wayyy cuter though. Who am I?",
      answer:"Kirby",
      options: [
        { label: "Kirby", value: "Kirby" },
        { label: "Bat Man", value: "Bat Man" },
        { label: "Home Lander", value: "Home Lander" },
        { label: "Start Light", value: "Start Light" },
      ],
    },
];

 const Chapters = [
  {
    title: "The Collector: Chapter 1",
    token:
      "47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974385379743367268",
    href: "https://opensea.io/assets/0x495f947276749ce646f68ac8c248420045cb7b5e/47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974385379743367268",
    count: 0,
  },
  {
    title: "The Collector: Chapter 2",
    token:
      "47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974386479254995044",
    href: "https://opensea.io/assets/0x495f947276749ce646f68ac8c248420045cb7b5e/47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974386479254995044",
    count: 0,
  },

  {
    title: "The Collector: Chapter 3",
    token:
      "47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974388678278250621",
    href: "https://opensea.io/assets/0x495f947276749ce646f68ac8c248420045cb7b5e/47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974388678278250621",
    count: 0,
  },

  {
    title: "The Collector: Chapter 4",
    token:
      "47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974389777789878397",
    href: "https://opensea.io/assets/0x495f947276749ce646f68ac8c248420045cb7b5e/47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974389777789878397",
    count: 0,
  },

  {
    title: "The Collector: Chapter 5",
    token:
      "47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974390877301506198",
    href: "https://opensea.io/assets/0x495f947276749ce646f68ac8c248420045cb7b5e/47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974390877301506198",
    count: 0,
  },

  {
    title: "The Collector: Tribute I",
    token:
      "47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974393076324762300",
    href: "https://opensea.io/assets/0x495f947276749ce646f68ac8c248420045cb7b5e/47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974393076324762300",
    count: 0,
  },
  {
    title: "The Collector: Chapter 6",
    token:
      "47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974396374859645078",
    href: "https://opensea.io/assets/0x495f947276749ce646f68ac8c248420045cb7b5e/47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974396374859645078",
    count: 0,
  },
  {
    title: "The Collector: MintPass",
    token:
      "47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974394175836389476",
    href: "https://opensea.io/assets/0x495f947276749ce646f68ac8c248420045cb7b5e/47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974394175836389476",
    count: 0,
  },
  {
    title: "The Collector: Chapter 7",
    token:
      "47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974397474371272904",
    href: "https://opensea.io/assets/0x495f947276749ce646f68ac8c248420045cb7b5e/47528499564916269558354577460055188011478914920306765323556974397474371272904",
    count:0
  },
];

 const redirectUrl ="https://thecollectorchronicles.io/home/user-profile/";

 const tokenContractAddress ="0x495f947276749Ce646f68AC8c248420045cb7b5e";
 
 const abi = [
  {
    inputs: [
      {
        internalType: "address",
        name: "account",
        type: "address",
      },
      {
        internalType: "uint256",
        name: "id",
        type: "uint256",
      },
    ],
    name: "balanceOf",
    outputs: [
      {
        internalType: "uint256",
        name: "",
        type: "uint256",
      },
    ],
    stateMutability: "view",
    type: "function",
  },
];

module.exports = {QuestionsList,Chapters,abi,tokenContractAddress};